// Easy Questions nested data structure
const easyQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'What was the first Marvel movie ever made?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Iron Man',},
            { text: 'Thor',},
            { text: 'Captain America',},
            { text: 'The Incredible Hulk',}
        ],

        answer: 'Iron Man'
    },

    {
        question: "What is Black Panther's suit made of?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Titanium'},
            { text: 'Carbon Fibre'},
            { text: 'Vibranium'},
            { text: 'Kevlar'}
        ],

        answer: 'Vibranium'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which actor voices the character of Groot?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Bradley Cooper'},
            { text: 'Vin Diesel'},
            { text: 'Jeremy Renner'},
            { text: 'Mark Ruffalo'}
        ],

        answer: 'Vin Diesel'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is Korg made of?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Iron'},
            { text: 'Scissors'},
            { text: 'Paper'},
            { text: 'Rock'}
        ],

        answer: 'Rock'
    },

    {
        question: "What is Tony Stark's father's name?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Howard'},
            { text: 'Steve'},
            { text: 'James'},
            { text: 'Peter'}
        ],

        answer: 'Howard'
    },

    {
        question: 'What video game does Thor get addicted to in Avengers: Endgame?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Street Fighter'},
            { text: 'Need For Speed'},
            { text: 'Super Mario'},
            { text: 'Fortnite'}
        ],

        answer: 'Fortnite'
    },

    {
        question: 'Who did Captain America give his shield to in Avengers: Endgame?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Falcon'},
            { text: 'Iron Man'},
            { text: 'Black Widow'},
            { text: 'The Winter Soldier'}
        ],

        answer: 'Falcon'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the name of the agency led by Red Skull?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Sinister Six'},
            { text: 'Hydra'},
            { text: 'A.I.M'},
            { text: 'Hellfire Club'}
        ],

        answer: 'Hydra'
    },

    {
        question: 'Where does Hank Pym keep an army tank in Ant-Man?',
        options: [
            { text: 'His keychain'},
            { text: 'His Garage'},
            { text: 'His Office'},
            { text: 'His Warehouse'}
        ],

        answer: 'His keychain'
    },

    {
        question: "What is Agent Coulson's first name?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Bill'},
            { text: 'Jason'},
            { text: 'Phil'},
            { text: 'Steven'}
        ],

        answer: 'Phil'
    }
];

// Medium Questions nested data structure
const mediumQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'Which billionaire makes a cameo in Iron Man 2?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Richard Branson'},
            { text: 'Elon Musk'},
            { text: 'Mark Zuckerberg'},
            { text: 'Jeff Bezos'}
        ],

        answer: 'Elon Musk'
    },

    {
        question: "Who is Black Panther's little sister?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Shuri'},
            { text: 'Okoye'},
            { text: 'Nakia'},
            { text: 'Ramonda'}
        ],

        answer: 'Shuri'
    },

    {
        question: 'What object does Goose swallow in Captain Marvel?',
        options: [
            { text: 'A transponder'},
            { text: "Fury's eye patch"},
            { text: 'The Tesseract'},
            { text: 'Ship keys'}
        ],

        answer: 'The Tesseract'
    },

    {
        question: 'What were the last words said by Thanos in Avengers: Endgame?',
        options: [
            { text: 'I am a survivor'},
            { text: 'A small price to pay for salvation'},
            { text: 'Perfectly balanced as all things should be'},
            { text: 'I am inevitable'}
        ],

        answer: 'I am inevitable'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which Avenger does Loki enslave in The Avengers?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Hawkeye'},
            { text: 'Hulk'},
            { text: 'Iron Man'},
            { text: 'Captain America'}
        ],

        answer: 'Hawkeye'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the name of the protocol that Tony Star enacts in Iron Man 3?',
        options: [
            { text: 'The Doomsday Protocol'},
            { text: 'The Contingency Plan Protocol'},
            { text: 'The Clean Slate Protocol'},
            { text: 'The Full Eclipse Protocol'}
        ],

        answer: 'The Clean Slate Protocol'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which infinity stone do the Guardians have to save in Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 1?',
        options: [
            { text: 'The power stone'},
            { text: 'The reality stone'},
            { text: 'The space stone'},
            { text: 'The time stone'}
        ],

        answer: 'The power stone'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the name of the drone piloted by Sam Wilson in Captain America: Civil War?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Dart'},
            { text: 'Redwing'},
            { text: 'Night Hawk'},
            { text: 'Sparrow'}
        ],

        answer: 'Redwing'
    },

    {
        question: "What are the names of Wanda's kids?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Danny and Johnny'},
            { text: 'Reiley and Lewis'},
            { text: 'Billy and Tommy'},
            { text: 'Charlie and Peter'}
        ],

        answer: 'Billy and Tommy'
    },

    {
        question: "What is the name of the dwarf who made Thanos' gauntlet?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Gimli'},
            { text: 'Andvari'},
            { text: 'FÃ¡fnir'},
            { text: 'Eitiri'}
        ],

        answer: 'Eitiri'
    }
];

// Hard Questions nested data structure
const hardQuestions = [
    {
        question: 'What type of doctor is Dr. Strange?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Neurosurgeon'},
            { text: 'Orthopaedic surgeon'},
            { text: 'General surgeon'},
            { text: 'Cardiothoracic surgeon'}
        ],

        answer: 'Neurosurgeon'
    },

    {
        question: "What animal does Darren Cross unsuccessfully use as test subjects in Ant-Man?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Rats'},
            { text: 'Lambs'},
            { text: 'Rabbits'},
            { text: 'Goats'}
        ],

        answer: 'Lambs'
    },

    {
        question: 'Which Spongebob character does Tony call Ebony Maw in Avengers: Infinity War?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Patrick'},
            { text: "Krabs"},
            { text: 'Plankton'},
            { text: 'Squidward'}
        ],

        answer: 'Squidward'
    },

    {
        question: 'Who was the main foe in Thor: Dark World?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Malekith'},
            { text: 'Kurse'},
            { text: 'Collector' },
            { text: 'Volstagg'}
        ],

        answer: 'Malekith'
    },

    {
        question: "How many legs does Odin's horse have?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Four'},
            { text: 'Ten'},
            { text: 'Eight'},
            { text: 'Six'}
        ],

        answer: 'Eight'
    },

    {
        question: 'How many years was Steve Rogers trapped under the ice?',
        options: [
            { text: '66 Years'},
            { text: '50 Years'},
            { text: '78 years'},
            { text: '35 Years'}
        ],

        answer: '66 Years'
    },

    {
        question: 'What is the name of the call sign Carol Danvers and Maria use in Captain Marvel?',
        options: [
            { text: 'Nova'},
            { text: 'Photon'},
            { text: 'Rogue'},
            { text: 'Atlas'}
        ],

        answer: 'Photon'
    },

    {
        question: "What percentage success rate was Tony's time travel test in Avengers: Endgame?",
        options: [
            { text: '98.837%'},
            { text: '100%'},
            { text: '96.244%'},
            { text: '99.987%'}
        ],

        answer: '99.987%'
    },

    {
        question: "In Avengers: Infinity War, what is Drax eating when he's watching Peter and Gamora kiss?",
        options: [
            { text: 'Puffies'},
            { text: 'Zarg Nuts'},
            { text: 'Yaro Root'},
            { text: 'Sugar Snaps'}
        ],

        answer: 'Zarg Nuts'
    },

    {
        question: "What university's name is on the sweatshirt worn by Dr. Strange when Peter visits him at his Sanctum Santorum in Spider-Man: No Way Home?",
        options: [
            { text: 'California'},
            { text: 'Louisiana'},
            { text: 'Columbia'},
            { text: 'Massachusetts'}
        ],

        answer: 'Columbia'
    }
];